

I am a Full-Stack developer graduated from Henry. I have professional experience as a freelance developer. My favorite aspect of programming is problemsolving and the freedom to create features for addressing issues. My main technological stack includes React, Next.js, Node.js, and PostgreSQL. I consider myself a good team player, responsible, and quick

If you need further adjustments or have additional information to include, feel free to let me know!

Digital Tools		Soft skills
HTML	Boostrap	Creativity
CSS	Redux	Teamwork
JavaScript	Express	Excellent
React	Sequelize	Communication
Node.js	PostgreSQL	Problem-Solving
Git	Figma	
Tailwind	Framer Motion	

Languages

 \rightarrow Spanish Native

Ingles Intermedio (B2 Upper Intermidiate)

Contact

→ aronresni@gmail.com

→ +54 9 3413770976

→ Santa Fe, Argentina

ron Resnicoff

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Experience

Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

Front-end Developer Intern

<u>LinkedIn</u> Portfolio Github

No-Country

- · Internship at No-Country, working as a full-stack developer.
- Frontend: React, Redux, Tailwind CSS, CSS, Next.js.
- Backend: Node.js, Sequelize, Express, JWT (Json Web
- Database: PostgreSQL. Tools: Git, GitHub, Jira, Trello, Confluence, Slack.
- Agile: Scrum.

Jan 2023 - Present

Systems and Administrative Assistant

- · At Nutrisery, I am responsible for keeping computer systems up-to-date, regularly performing hardware upgrades, and configuring software settings. I also maintain the company's website.
- Additionally, I handle administrative tasks during the remaining time.

Educación

Jan 2023

Bachelor of Systems Engineering (1st Year)

· National Technological University

Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

Full-Stack Developer Bootcamp

800 hours of theoretical and practical

coursework.

Nov 2022 - Jul 2023

React Front-End Development Program

Coder House

Projects

Access Bank

- Developed back-end routes with Node.js, using Express and Sequelize.
- Managed various front-end components using React with Redux for state management.
- Implemented Chart.js to render various investment charts on
- Deployment on Github.

Deploy

Github

Listo para llevar

- Solely responsible for the front-end with React and implementation of libraries to render maps for business and user locations.
- Applied Tailwind CSS to components.
- · Deployment on Github.

Deploy

Github

Canchas Ya

- Integrated payments with Mercado Pago.
- · Connected with Cloudinary API to store court images.
- · Implemented Redux for main card requests.
- · Deployment on Github.

Deploy

Github